Guide to the Sutter Creek Store Records, 1866-1893 JL008
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Sutter Creek Store Records,
1866-1893
JL008
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
63.0 Linear feet
Sutter Creek store
Scope and Content
The records of the Sutter Creek store of Lawrence and C. Soracco are dated 1866-1893, and consist of daybooks, cash books, a purchase book, customers' account books, ledgers. The store was established in 1860 and the date of its dissolution is unknown.
Provenance
Gift of Frank Soracco to Jackson Library of Business. Transferred to the Department of Special Collections, 1979.
Access Restrictions
None.
- Daybook, June-Nov 1866 (Volume 1)
- Daybook, Nov 1866-April 1867 (Box 2)
- Daybook, April-Oct 1867 (Box 2)
- Daybook, Oct 1867-April 1868 (Box 2)
- Daybook, Oct 1869-Jan 1870 (Box 2)
- Daybook, April-Aug 1870 (Box 2)
- Daybook, Aug-Nov 1870 (Box 2)
- Daybook, Nov 1870-Feb 1871 (Box 3)
- Daybook, Feb-April 1871 (Box 3)
- Daybook, April-Aug 1871 (Box 3)
- Daybook, Oct 1871-Jan 1872 (Box 3)
- Daybook, Jan-March 1872 (Box 3)
- Daybook, March-May 1872 (Box 3)
- Daybook, June-Aug 1872 (Box 3)
- Daybook, Aug-Sept 1872 (Box 4)
- Daybook, Nov 1872-Aug 1873 (Box 4)
- Daybook, Aug 1873-Feb 1874 (Box 4)
- Daybook, Feb-July 1874 (Box 4)
- Daybook, July-Dec 1874 (Box 4)
- Daybook, Dec 1874-Feb 1875 (Box 5)
- Daybook, Feb-May 1875 (Box 5)
- Daybook, May-July 1875 (Box 5)
- Daybook, July-Nov 1875 (Box 5)
- Daybook, March-July 1876 (Box 5)
- Daybook, July-Sept 1876 (Box 5)
- Daybook, Sept-Dec 1876 (Box 6)
- Daybook, Dec 1876-May 1877 (Box 6)
- Daybook, May-Aug 1877 (Box 6)
- Daybook, Feb-July 1878 (Box 6)
- Daybook, Nov 1878-May 1879 (Volume 7)
- Daybook, May-Oct 1879 (Volume 8)
- Daybook, Oct 1879-April 1880 (Volume 9)
- Daybook, April-Dec 1880 (Volume 10)
- Daybook, Jan-June 1881 (Volume 11)
- Daybook, June-Nov 1881 (Volume 12)
- Daybook, Nov 1881-July 1882 (Volume 13)
- Daybook, July 1882-April 1883 (Volume 14)
- Daybook, April 1883-April 1884 (Volume 15)
- Daybook, April 1884-Feb 1885 (Volume 16)
- Daybook, March 1885-Jan 1886 (Volume 17)
- Daybook, Jan-June 1886 (Volume 18)
- Daybook, June-Nov 1886 (Volume 19)
- Daybook, Dec 1886-May 1887 (Volume 20)
- Daybook, March-Aug 1888 (Volume 21)
- Cash book, 1879-1883 (Box 22)
- Cash book, 1883-1893 (Box 22)
- Cash book, Feb-May 1893 (Box 22)
- Purchase book, 1879 (Box 22)
- Customers' accounts, 1868-1872 (Box 22)
- Customers' accounts, 1870-1871
- Customers' accounts, 1872-1876
- Customers' accounts, 1875-1877 (Volume 23)
- Ledger, 1867-1870 (Volume 24)
- Ledger, 1877-1879
- Ledger, 1880-1885
- Ledger, 1885-1887
- Ledger, 1883-1890
- Ledger, 1893
- Ledger, no date
- Ledger, no date
- Ledger, no date
- P.B. & Co. daybook, 1867 (Box 25)
- P.B. & Co. daybook, 1867-1868